It's my favorite time. It is project
time. Um, it is time to apply what
you've just learned. So, what I would
like you to do is I have given you three
APIs and those are not the right APIs.
Those are the right APIs. Sorry. I've
updated this project cuz one of the APIs
doesn't work the way I thought it did
when I put the video together and you
would need to have learned some things I
haven't taught you yet. So, swap the
project out a little bit. So, what I
want you to do is I want you to wire up
the HTML so that you can get a random
dog. Um, you can get a random piece of
advice and you can get a random joke.
And, um, I'll show you what
the UI looks like. Um, so here you have
it. When you click this get dog, I want
you to show the dog picture here. When
you click this get advice, I want you to
show the piece of advice here. And when
you click this get advice, oh, that
should say get joke. it will say get
joke by the time this video is done. Um,
this will say get joke and it will
display the joke here. And I've provided
all of those URLs for you. Um, so good
luck.